嗯  后来呢?
Yes, go on.
突然  猴子哭了
Suddenly the monkey starts crying.
-可怜的东西  -我回头一看
-Oh, poor thing. -I turned around and there's
-一大群全部都跑出来了  -什么? 什么呀
-a whole fleet of them! -Of what?
一大群的大猴子呀
There's an army of monkeys.
谁? 猴子
Monkeys? Monkeys!
对着我叫
Screaming at me!
她学的是一种狒狒
That's theripithicus baboonus.
-她学的最像了  -哦  是吗?
-She's very good at this. -Oh, really?
好可怕  把我吓坏了
Terrified I was. Terrified.
突然我在树上荡过来荡过去
And suddenly, I was swinging in the vines.
跟那些狒狒?
With the monkeys, yes?
荡呀  飞呀  在半空中
Swinging, flying. I was in the air.
半空中? 然后呢?
In the air, yes, I know.
-然后他们围着我  -那你怎么办
-And I'm all surrounded. -What did you do?
爸爸... 他们拿走了我的靴子
And daddy, they took my boot.
拿走了  那是我买的
They took... Those are the ones I bought you.
我就被救啦
And I was saved!
我是被一个腰上围块布的野人救下来
I was saved by a flying wild man in a loincloth.